I 'd better go now .
I ...
This isn 't like me .
Are you ashamed ?
No .
But ... I don 't know .
It 's okay . Really . I know what you 're feeling .
Are you scared ?
No .
Frightened eyes never lie .
I saw ...
I saw lights , you know ?
Bright spots flying around .
I saw them , too . Flying around really fast .
I saw them as if they were burned onto my retina .
But ...
I saw myself when I was in school ,
wearing my uniform .
You 're going to laugh .
I saw myself in the confessional with Father Miguel .
I 'd better go .
You 're regretting this , aren 't you ?
I don 't know .
Ask me tomorrow .
We should run away ,
so you don 't have to deal with this anymore ...
- Who could that be ? - I don 't know .
Please , I don 't want anyone to know I 'm here .
His face ... his eyes ...
Did you see his eyes ?
Finally , some peace and quiet .
About time , right ?
One starts to worry when children are so quiet .
- What happened ? - Sara 's hurt .
Hurt how ?
I didn 't do anything . She just started bleeding .
Don 't worry , I 'll go .
No , Adolfo , come here . Stay here with me .
What happened , Sara ?
Tell me .
Don 't worry , okay ?
It 's completely normal .
You 'll be fine .
Don 't worry .
It 's not unusual .
Mom gets them , too .
Every woman , after a certain age ,
loses a little blood once a month .
Once a month ? Always ?
Well , for many , many years .
Except when they 're pregnant .
Not when they 're pregnant ?
But don 't worry . It 's normal .
Sarita , I 'll wash that in a second .
Now , take this , clean yourself .
Everything 's fine , okay ?
What 's up ?
Hey ..
The kids want to go to that hill for a little while .
Are you serious ?
I 'm not saying we have to go . I 'm saying they want to go .
You want to take a nap ?
Let me think about it . Take this .
What about Sarita ?
What about her ?
Is she able to go like that ?
It 's just her period . She 's not handicapped .
Go on . Park the car .
Okay , but stay together , all right ?
I want you back in an hour .
Mom , that 's barely enough time to get there and back !
Okay , an hour and a half .
No more . It 's getting late .
I 'm serious , Sara . Otherwise , you don 't go .
Take my watch and keep track of the time . Seriously !
- Yes , mom . - Okay ?
- Okay . - And don 't talk to strangers .
What , Felix ?
You look beautiful today .
Yeah , right . I look horrible in this heat .
That 's not true .
It 's too hot in here , Felix . Let 's just take a nap .
When was the last time we did something ?
So it 's my fault ?
Don 't get defensive . I 'm just asking .
I don 't remember . The kids are always around .
They 're not here now .
It 's hot in here , and we 're at a truck stop .
Not exactly romantic .
Always something .
Do you remember what happened last time ?
Yeah , you remember .
There you were , with your naked hairy ass ...
It 's no big deal . Happens to a lot of kids .
Did it happen to you ?
No , but seeing your parents making love
isn 't the end of the world .
Adolfo 's a smart kid .
It has nothing to do with intelligence .
Kids need to find out about those things differently .
When I was 13 ,
my father gave me a nudie magazine .
He said he had found it ...
and asked me to take a look .
I knew he had bought it for me .
He never said anything else about it .
He felt that a magazine had all the instructions I ever needed .
Your father always was a brute . Just like you .
What he didn 't know
is that I 'd already learned about it .
Before you were 13 ? With who ?
A girl from my neighborhood .
She showed me her breasts .
And then I showed her my dick .
And she showed me her pussy .
And what did you do to her ?
I touched her pussy .
Did you like it ?
Yes , it was soft .
Very little hair .
Then I smelled it . It smelled like pee .
- Did you fuck her ? - Of course not .
I couldn 't do much . I just rubbed against her ,
but we stopped because we didn 't know what we were doing .
- You 're wet . - No , it 's just the heat .
And you ?
Did you show it to someone ?
Yes .
Where ?
At camp .
He was 15 . I was 13 .
- What did he do ? - He took me aside ,
said he had something important to tell me .
And what did he say ?
He stuck his tongue in my mouth .
And then ?
He pressed his cock against me and started rubbing .
Yeah ?
We didn 't do anything because we didn 't know how .
And then ?
He said he would show me something if I did the same .
- What did you show him ? - My pussy .
- Did he touch it ? - No , he kissed it .
- Was it nice ? - It tickled .
And then ?
He showed me his dick .
I thought it was enormous .
Did you blow him ?
No , dear .
He wanted me to , but I didn 't .
You blew him , didn 't you ?
Yes .
I swallowed some of his cum .
Don 't stop , Felix .
You were a little slut , weren 't you ?
Yes .
What time did you tell them to be back ?
Adolfo !
Sara !
Nobody should go up there .
Some folks think there 's an energy there ,
but something 's wrong with that place .
The Indians who lived in this area
believed the hill had power , but they never got closer .
It was considered a cursed place .
It 's true .
They said there were living beings who slept in the depths ,
creatures that think we 're nothing more than shells .
I understand .
Believe me , we 're going to do everything we can to help ,
but we can 't start searching right now .
We have to wait until sunrise .
Look , there 's a hotel nearby .
You should get some rest . It 's for the best .
What if they come back and we 're not here ?
Ma 'am , we 'll stay here in case they come back .
Sir . Sir !
Tomorrow is going to be a long day ,
so we need you to get some rest .
Are you really going to watch TV , Felix ?
What ?
Are you really going to watch TV ?
No , I 'm not . It 's too quiet , okay ?
Too quiet ?
I just don 't want to be in silence , okay ?
How curious .
You 're a bitch .
- What did you call me ? - I said you 're a bitch !
But what you always complain about .
You can 't work at home
because the kids are too loud all the time .
And I 'm the bitch ?
So it 's my fault that they got lost , right ?
- Yes , it 's your fault . - Oh , really ? My fault ?
I let them go on their own
because you never want to do anything with them !
Never ? That 's why we 're here !
Never ! All family plans bother you ,
everything makes you angry ...
Everything ! Everything ! That 's why we 're here !
And the kids ? That 's why we 're alone .
- Go to hell ! - You go to hell .
No ! You go to hell !
Don 't touch me ! Get the fuck out !
Get out ! Don 't touch me !
What is that ?
We were in a cave . It was so dark .
We didn 't know where to go .
Take it easy . You 're home now .
Everything 's gonna be fine .
Listen , the most important thing is that you can 't be scared .
You 're in control . Just keep moving forward .
Let 's go . Straight on .
There you go .
Try to brake slower .
Slowly , slowly .
You okay ?
Felix , are you awake ?
Hey , Sara .
Where did you leave your panties ?
The ones from the other night .
The stained ones .
I washed them at the gas station ,
and you wore them again .
I put them with the laundry .
No , they 're not there .
Did you leave them somewhere else ?
Did you handle the pads yourself ?
For the blood ?
I 'm not bleeding anymore .
Adolfo , don 't be rude .
Go and get your things for school .
You ready ? Come on . I 'm gonna be late .
Take Adolfo to school .
I 'm taking Sara to see the doctor .
Girl stuff .
Put on your seatbelt .
See , Sara ? No big deal .
Wait outside , darling . I 'll be there soon .
Nothing to be alarmed about .
Sometimes first periods are irregular .
Nothing unusual about that .
That makes me feel better .
But there 's something else . Listen to me carefully .
Your daughter doesn 't have a hymen .
But that , in principle , doesn 't suggest anything .
Many women are born without one
and others tear it accidentally in childhood .
It 's perfectly normal .
It 's not an indication that sexual intercourse
or abuse has occurred .
But there is that possibility ?
We would need to do further tests to find out .
I think it best you talk with your daughter first .
If you believe something has occurred ,
then you should speak with the police
and bring Sara back for more tests .
Did you like the doctor ?
I told you there was nothing to worry about .
Sara .
Did you and Adolfo meet anyone when you were on the hill ?
- Was anyone else there ? - No .
My specialty is kids
and I assure you , it takes time .
There 's no magic key to open the psyche of a child .
But did they say anything ?
I asked each one separately to draw the place
where they got lost .
They made several drawings ,
but it 's interesting
that they both drew very similar things .
Do you think something bad happened ?
It 's risky to draw conclusions .
But what do you think ?
There 's no doubt that being lost at night
is a traumatic experience for any child .
The feeling of abandonment , of being alone in the world ,
is overwhelming for anyone of any age .
I think they will tell us more . It just takes time .
They look a little scary .
Think so ?
The colors ... I don 't know .
It was nighttime .
Not so odd that they used dark colors .
Maybe . But why did they both draw our car ?
Let me see .
What 's wrong ?
What is it ?
It 's not our car .
What do you mean it 's not our car ?
It 's a pickup truck that was there that night .
Was someone else on the hill ?
I only saw the truck .
- Good morning . - Good morning .
I 'm looking for the officer who was on-duty Saturday night .
My kids went missing , and he helped us find them .
You 're the father ?
Yes , you were lucky .
Too many people have disappeared up there .
- Really ? - You 're not from around here ?
That 's right . Do you remember Ismael Arau ?
- The serial killer ? - That 's the one .
His last victim wounded him .
He couldn 't possibly have survived it .
They found traces of his blood going up the hill .
They found his machete , but never his body .
He disappeared into thin air , and he isn 't the only one .
Your stories are boring the man .
You 're looking for Sergeant Flores .
He 's not here today . It 's his day off .
If you want to leave your number ,
I 'll let him know you 're looking for him .
Did everything pan out all right ?
Your kids got lost the other day .
They found them on the road .
Yes , they 're fine . Thanks .
Did the earthquake scare them ?
Earthquake ?
No one mentioned it , but there was one that night .
Yes , I think I felt it .
Did they get scared ?
They haven 't said anything .
Do you know someone with an old truck with red lights ?
Yes . Why ?
I wanted to thank him . He helped us out .
Lucio helped you ?
What a surprise . That boy doesn 't speak much .
- Lucio . - He 's a strange guy .
But you can 't judge a book by its cover , right ?
Do you know where I can find him ?
He lives over there in a trailer on the other side of the hill .
But I don 't think he 's there now .
He works full-time . He supplies us with some stuff .
He 's not coming in today , but he 'll be here tomorrow .
He works in the city .
I can give you the address of his wholesaler .
He should be there tomorrow morning .
That would be great .
Are you okay ?
We saw the psychologist again .
And ?
He says we have to be very cautious .
Cautious ?
Yes .
There 're some signs ... of ...
Signs of what , Sol ?
Of a traumatic ...
sexual incident .
Sarita .
Let 's go .
Where are we going , Mom ?
We have something to do . Hurry up .
What happened to you ?
- Does it hurt ? - No .
Are you sure this is the place ?
That 's what he told me .
What if somebody warned him , Felix ?
This is a loading zone . Please move your car .
We 're waiting for someone . He 'll be here any minute now .
You 've been here for over an hour .
You 're going to get me in trouble .
- We 're about to leave . - Please do .
It 's him .
Sara , Sara , wake up .
I need you to tell me if you recognize that truck .
Hi , kids !
Say hi to Marcia , kids .
It 's all right . They 're watching TV .
- You know how kids are . - Yeah .
Why did you think I couldn 't make it ?
I thought it was too short notice .
How many times have I offered ?
I know .
They have grown so much .
Yes , they have .
Sara is almost a woman !
Take it easy .
Take whatever you want .
Lucio .
How do you know my name ?
Because we 're the devil , and we 've come for you .
Put your hands together .
Just take whatever you want .
Did you not hear me ? Put them together !
Don 't you move .
What 'd I do to you ?
What you did no longer matters .
What matters now is what you 'll never be able to do again .
Tell us exactly what happened .
When ?
Saturday . On the hill .
What are you talking about ?
It wasn 't your first time , right ?
What was on your mind when you saw them ?
I didn 't see anybody .
You kept a souvenir , right ?
I didn 't ... I didn 't take anything .
Listen to me . I 'll only say this once .
This is your last chance . Just tell us the truth .
Tell us what you did on Saturday .
No one else will ever know . Just us , Lucio .
You found them on the hill .
- Who ? - The kids , Lucio .
Our kids .
You don 't know what we 're talking about ? Is that it ?
Yes . Yes , the kids ... they were there .
And what exactly did you do ?
I didn 't do anything . I only saw them there .
What did you take for yourself ?
I didn 't take anything .
Listen ! Listen to me .
If you don 't tell us the truth , I will hurt you .
I will hurt you very ... very ... much .
You kept them , didn 't you ?
Where are they ?
I ... I won 't say a thing .
I promise I won 't say anything to anybody .
Don 't you understand , Lucio ?
You have to tell us .
You have to tell us everything .
I can 't . I 'm scared .
At least tell me one thing ...
where did you put them ?
They were there on the counter . I only ... I only took them .
Where are they ?
What is it ? Sol ?
I 'm sorry . They were there on the ground .
I don 't know what I was thinking .
Shut up !
What 's wrong ?
What is it , Sol ?
Marcia .
Marcia ?
I 'll see if she 's upstairs .
- Okay . - Marcia ?
The kids are asleep , but she 's gone .
- Are they all right ? - Yeah , but she 's not here .
Call her .
She 's not answering .
Hello ?
This is Ana , the principal at your children 's school .
I 'm calling because we 're a little concerned .
I have reports ...
from Sara 's and Adolfo 's teachers
that they 've been behaving strangely .
We wanted to know if everything is all right at home .
Yes . We had a family situation .
It 's a delicate matter .
I 'm sorry . I didn 't mean to intrude .
No , it 's okay .
But since the kids have been absent the last few days ,
We were wondering what happened
and if we can be of any assistance .
No . It 's okay . We 're ... we 're working on it .
I 'm glad to hear that .
Do you know when the kids will be coming back ?
You can pick up their assignments
so they don 't fall behind .
Yes . You know what ?
I 'll call you back in a minute . Thank you for calling .
Well , you can rely on us . Bye now .
Hi .
How was school ?
Fine .
Yes , fine .
Dinner is almost ready .
Sara !
Sara ! Wake up ! Wake up ! Sara !
We should call the police .
I think someone was trying to scare us .
I think someone knows .
No . How ?
Maybe someone saw us .
Why not ?
Because it doesn 't make sense .
How do you explain what just happened ?
I don 't know .
Maybe someone saw us .
He followed us and came here to scare us .
What about all those noises ?
Rocks .
Then why did they all stop at once ?
I don 't know , Sol .
Maybe all the yelling scared them off .
And why didn 't the kids wake up ?
- What do you mean ? - Don 't you think it was weird ?
I 'll be home late . I have some things to do .
Me , too . I 'm taking the kids to the psychologist after school .
I checked outside for rocks .
None . Nothing broken .
- Hi . - Good morning .
- May I come in ? - Of course . Sorry .
How 're the kids doing ?
Fine , thank you .
Sorry , did I come at a bad time ?
No , not at all .
Felix was about to take the kids to school .
It 's just that we weren 't expecting anyone .
How did you find us ?
I 'd like to say it was because I 'm a cop .
Truth is you gave me your contact information
when the kids disappeared .
Well , turns out there was a crime .
Particularly nasty one .
A man who lived in the area
where the kids disappeared was murdered .
It took some time to find the body .
It was an unpleasant scene .
I don 't want to take up too much of your time ,
but I think you knew him .
Us ?
Yes .
I believe you went to see him .
- Me ' ? - Yes , you .
The gas station employee told me you were asking for him
because he helped you somehow .
Lucio .
Sure , the guy with the truck .
Remember ? He helped us find the hotel when we got lost .
Oh , right .
- Is he dead ? - Yes , he 's dead .
He was a little odd . Not everyone liked him .
Some folks believed he had some ... vices .
I never knew for sure .
We had a good relationship .
And did you ever find him ?
You were looking to thank him , right ?
No , I couldn 't find him .
That 's a shame .
You see , I 'm trying to reconstruct his final days .
I see , but this isn 't your jurisdiction , right ?
Right .
And it 's not my case , either . I 'm just trying to help .
I thought you wouldn 't mind . I didn 't mean to trouble you .
No trouble . I 'm just surprised .
Anything else ?
No , that 's it for today .
By the way ,
I heard that you had asked for me
at the station that day .
Yes , I wanted to thank you for finding my kids .
Thanks .
Goodbye .
Goodbye , madam .
Say hi to the kids .
See ? I told you .
What ?
He knows .
Ready ? Let 's go , then .
- Hi . - Hi .
- How was school ? - Normal .
Madam ...
it seems your kids have developed a bond ,
one tighter than usual in siblings of that age .
What do you mean ?
It might be best if they go to different schools ,
have different activities , do things separately .
Excessive dependence
on one another can be harmful
to certain processes that occur at that age .
What are you doing ?
I was ... I 'm looking for Sarita 's blanket .
She was cold last night . Do you know where it is ?
The blankets are down there .
Where ?
Felix , I need to talk to you .
- What is it ? - The kids .
What about them ?
Have you thought about ... what if we were wrong ?
We did what we thought was right ,
but what if we were wrong ?
I don 't know what you 're talking about .
Lucio .
Listen carefully .
This is the last time I say this .
I will not talk about that ever again .
You hear me ? It 's over .
Where did you get that ?
Go and check on the kids . Go !
Mom ?
Where did you get that gun ?
I bought it . We need protection .
You got any doubts about what 's going on now ?
Do you really think somebody comes every night
to throw rocks at our house and then disappear ?
Well , then tell me what you think .
I think there 's something terrible going on .
Of course there is . There 's no doubt about that .
But it 's our kids ...
they 're not the same . Something 's changed .
Of course something 's changed !
Remember what happened to them ?
Maybe we misunderstood something .
Maybe I made a mistake .
I told you I won 't talk about that again .
Listen to me .
Something is wrong with our kids .
And the noises ? What about them ?
I think the kids are causing them .
I think you 're losing your mind .
Marcia .
What happened the other night ?
Nothing .
You can tell me , Marcia .
I know something 's wrong .
I need you to help me find out what .
We 've always been friends . I need you now .
Did you hear noises ?
Yes .
I heard ...
Tell me .
We had dinner together .
We watched TV .
They were ...
Quiet ?
Lifeless .
Suddenly everything went dark .
I don 't know how that happened .
Then I saw something .
I can 't describe it ...
But it dragged me away .
I felt powerless .
And then I clearly felt
two cold feet
standing on my chest , paralyzing me .
I 've never believed in God .
You know that .
But I remembered a painting I saw once .
It was of what happened to me .
It was the devil .
The devil stood on my chest .
Who took your clothes off ?
I don 't know .
It happened while I was asleep .
But then ...
something worse happened .
- I can 't tell you . - I need to know .
I felt like it wasn 't my body .
Then I heard it .
What ?
I can 't .
Marcia , what did you hear ?
They were moaning .
They were together .
Your kids ... their moaning ...
I woke up in your bed .
Maybe it was all just a dream , Marcia .
I don 't know . What do you think ?
It 's me .
Where are you ?
I 'm sorry . I went for a walk .
I had some things to do .
You should have told me .
I know , I 'm sorry .
Listen , yesterday I got a phone call from the school .
What did they say ?
They 're asking the parents
to walk their kids to the door from now on .
But it 's hard to find a parking spot .
I know , but it 's a safety issue .
So please walk them to the door
and wait until they get in .
Okay .
Are you all right ?
Yes , I 'm better now . Don 't worry .
What 's going on ?
The kids ..
What about them ?
I left them at the door like you said .
They didn 't go in .
Of course they did .
They were talking to their friends .
No .
Sol , I just left them .
What do you mean you just left them ?
It 's 7 : 15 .
What time did you leave them ?
You weren 't here , so breakfast took longer ,
then to find a parking spot ...
so I left them at 7 : 00 a.m. , just as the bell rang .
I 'll call you later .
What 's going on , Sol ?
What is this place ?
I don 't know .
My daughter was the last victim
of the worst serial killer we ever had .
Before she died , she saw his face .
And what she saw ... what she described was
nothing like the man they were after .
He wasn 't a man .
That morning , after he attacked my daughter ,
when he disappeared on the hill ,
we had an earthquake .
Just like the one on the night your kids disappeared .
Those who dwell there are in search of prey .
They 're hunting .
Hunting ?
They 're looking for the weak . People who can be possessed .
To them , we 're only a shell .
They use us to do evil and then throw us away .
That poor devil Lucio
believed that shrines and offerings would keep them away .
But they 've been here since the beginning of time .
They know how to survive .
Good afternoon .
Madam , we 've discovered something .
- Sugar ? - No thanks .
There 's a new statement
from the warehouse guard where Lucio used to work .
He says that he saw a car ...
a car like your husband 's .
He also said there was a couple and two kids inside .
The kids started to scream
and the car took off .
So ?
Maybe you went there to thank him ?
No .
Maybe you had another reason to go ?
Lucio was a strange guy ,
someone most people wouldn 't trust .
What are you trying to say ?
I 'm not so sure about him anymore .
Maybe he 's not worth the investigation .
If I knew that , I 'd be more discreet .
Why should it be like that ?
We 've learned that Lucio was a bit voyeuristic .
He used to take clothes
that didn 't belong to him .
Maybe he did something wrong ?
Thanks .
Well , that was all .
Great coffee .
Lucio was an odd fellow .
The day after your kids disappeared he called me ,
very upset .
He said he went to the hill to leave some candles .
He believed the place was cursed .
He said he found a boy
and a girl , both dead .
Dead ! Can you imagine that story ?
We had already found them on the road ,
so we never paid attention to it .
We thought it must 've been a delusion .
I guess ...
someone must 've told
him about the two missing children .
He described them fairly well .
Maybe ...
it was you ,
when you met him ?
No .
He saw them earlier ,
when we stopped at the gas station .
See you later .
The school called a little while ago .
Again ?
Two kids have chickenpox , so there 's no school tomorrow .
Well , what are we going to do ?
Don 't worry .
I 'll stay with them . You go to work .
We 'll find something fun to do . Right , guys ?
Is everything all right ?
Excuse me ?
The police were here yesterday .
Your wife let him in .
Everything 's fine . Thanks .
Okay .
Rise and shine .
Seize the day .
How do you like it ?
I don 't want juice .
I made it just for you .
I ain 't thirsty .
Drink it , Sara .
Drink it !
All right , then . Finish quickly .
I want you to change into your party clothes .
I 'm taking you to a very special place .
What 's up ?
Felix , listen to me ,
We have to meet . It 's very important .
What 's going on , Sol ? I 'm at work .
There 's something you have to see .
It 's very important .
Meet me at the gas station , near the hill .
But what 's the matter ?
See you there in an hour .
What 's going on ? Where are the kids ?
They 're fine . I left them with Marcia .
There 's something on the hill you have to see .
Come on !
Sol . Sol !
Where are we going ?
It 's here .
What ?
This is where your children went that night .
I 'm not going in there , Sol .
Don 't you want to know ?
- Know what ? - Come on !
Felix .
Felix , listen to me .
This will be difficult to understand .
I need you to be strong .
Over there .
Go on .
Go !
Be careful .
See ?
Do you see their clothes ?
That 's what they were wearing when they disappeared .
The children ...
our children never left this place .
Look at them ! Don 't you see ?
The only reason they were afraid of Lucio
was because he 'd seen their bodies .
Felix , look at them , please .
Do you hear me ?
HERE COMES THE DEVIL